Hey, don't take a detour here.
Hey, yolu buradan uzatmayalım.
Let's just go home already.
Eve gidelim artık.
Geez, I give up.
Tanrım, pes ediyorum.
I'm starving.
Açlıktan ölüyorum.
I have no money.
Hiç param yok.
If only that rug were still okay.
Keşke o kilime bir şey olmasaydı.
Dammit.
Lanet olsun.
Huh? What is that?
Ne? Bu ne?
This is…
Bu…
"Save me!"
"Kurtar beni.
"The monster inside me is about to burst out!"
İçimdeki canavar dışarı çıkmak üzere"
There are two individuals within Johan.
Johan'ın içinde iki kişi var.
So, what you're saying is…
Yani diyorsunuz ki
When you stopped by the warehouse,
deponun yanında durduğunuzda
that Asian guy and the arsonist were already in a scuffle.
Asyalı adam ve kundakçı tartışıyordu.
Then, the Asian guy noticed you were there and ran off.
Sonra Asyalı adam sizi görüp kaçtı.
Is that right, Ms. Anna Liebert?
Öyle mi Bayan Anna Liebert?
Yes.
Evet.
Well, the culprit is a member of the far-right
Suçu işleyen adam aşırı sağcı bir grup mensubu.
and has turned himself in, saying the flames were for a festival of race.
Yangınların ırk festivali için olduğunu söyleyerek suçunu itiraf etti.
Your personal references hold up,
Sizin söylediklerinizle de örtüşüyor,
so we can stop for today.
yani bugün bırakabiliriz.
Does that mean I can go home now?
Yani artık eve gidebilir miyim?
Yes.
Evet.
And also, the people of that district
Ayrıca o mahallenin sakinleri
called that Asian by the name of Dr. Tenma.
o Asyalı adamın Dr. Tenma olduğunu söyledi.
Do you know anything about him?
Onun hakkında bir bilginiz var mı?
I don't know anything.
Bir bilgim yok.
What do you think?
Ne düşünüyorsun?
Given her outfit, maybe she was trying to engage in prostitution in that district.
Kıyafetlerine bakılırsa
No.
Hayır.
What?
Ne?
I'm talking about Dr. Tenma.
Dr. Tenma'dan bahsediyorum.
At first, people from the Turkish District called the Asian man by that name.
Başta Türk Mahallesi'ndekiler Asyalı adamın adının bu olduğunu söyledi.
But when we began investigations and said he was a suspected serial killer,
Soruşturmaya başlayıp
they all would say the same thing.
hepsi aynı şeyi söyledi.
They'd say, "I don't know this man."
"Bu adamı tanımıyorum" dedi.
I acted as your guarantor.
Sana kefil oldum.
Mr. Rosso.
Bay Rosso.
Have you been well, Anna?
İyi misin Anna?
I've been worried about you.
Seni çok merak ettim.
You disappeared so suddenly.
Birden ortadan kayboldun.
Are you done changing?
Değiştirdin mi?
Yeah, that kind of outfit looks better on you.
Evet, bu tarz kıyafetler sana daha çok yakışıyor.
That look before didn't suit you.
Öncekiler yakışmıyordu.
Come. I bet you're hungry.
Gel, kesin açsındır.
Eat some food.
Bir şeyler ye.
Are you not eating, Mr. Rosso?
Siz yemiyor musunuz Bay Rosso?
I ate before I came here.
Ben gelmeden yedim.
I'll just have a coffee.
Sadece kahve içeceğim.
Come on. Eat.
Hadi, yesene.
Yes. Thank you for the food.
Tamam, yemek için sağ olun.
What is it?
Ne oldu?
Just like always, you put in five spoonfuls of sugar.
Her zamanki gibi beş kaşık şeker attınız.
Of course I did.
Herhâlde yani.
Coffee doesn't taste good unless it's sweet.
Tatlı olmayan kahvenin tadı kötü olur.
You finally smiled.
Nihayet gülümsedin.
What?
Ne?
You came to interview for a job, yet your face looked so gloomy.
İş görüşmesine geldin ama yüzün sirke satıyor.
Is it so strange to put in a lot of sugar?
Çok şeker atmak çok mu garip?
Anna, um…
Anna, şey…
Oh, it's Anna Liebert.
Adım Anna Liebert.
I, um…
Şey…
You're hired, of course.
İşe alındın tabii ki.
It's a no-brainer.
Düşünecek bir şey yok.
If a beauty like you works here,
Senin gibi bir güzel burada çalışırsa
our business will boom like crazy.
işlerimiz patlama yapar.
But…
Ama…
But?
Aması ne?
You should smile a bit more.
Biraz daha çok gülümsemelisin.
Your beauty will go to waste.
Yoksa güzelliğin boşa gider.
Thank you very much.
Çok teşekkürler.
I'll work hard.
Çok çalışacağım.
You don't have to strain yourself.
Kendini zorlamana gerek yok. Kırsal kesimde bir İtalyan restoranıyız.
Keeping busy won't amount to much.
Yoğun çalışmak pek bir işe yaramaz.
Go around the counter.
Tezgâhın önüne gel.
Okay.
Tamam.
I'll bring out the food here.
Yemeği buraya koyacağım.
You'll take it to the customer.
Sen de müşteriye götüreceksin.
Used plates are placed on the right side of the counter.
Kullanılmış tabaklar tezgâhın sağına konacak.
Wine goes here, and glasses are on this shelf.
Şaraplar buraya, bardaklar da bu rafa.
There's wine above the counter too.
Tezgâhın üstünde de şaraplar var.
Tickets with people's orders go here.
Siparişlerin yazdığı notlar buraya.
There's wine above the counter,
Tezgâhın üstünde şaraplar var,
and glasses are there.
bardaklar buraya.
This is the water.
Bu da su.
Okay.
Tamam.
Hello.
Merhaba.
Come on in.
Buyurun.
Welcome.
Hoş geldiniz.
I'm starving.
Kurt gibi açım.
What?
Ne?
Nice to meet you.
Memnun oldum.
I'm Anna.
Ben Anna.
"Nice to meet you"? Hold on.
"Memnun oldum" mu? Bir saniye.
You can't possibly be the waitress at a place like this, right?
Sen böyle bir restoranın garsonu olamazsın, değil mi?
What?
Ne?
What do you mean, "a place like this"?
"Böyle bir restoranın" ne demek?
Anna is, without a doubt, a waitress here starting today.
Anna yeni garsonumuz, bugün işe başladı.
I'll do my best.
Elimden geleni yapacağım.
Are you serious?
Ciddi misin?
Well, isn't that something.
Bak şu işe.
What's this?
Ne bu?
Anna, can I have a carbonara?
Anna, carbonara alabilir miyim?
Anna, I'll have a bolognese.
Anna, ben de bolonez alayım.
Anna, can you come and pour me some water?
Anna, bana su koyar mısın?
Yes, right away.
Tabii, hemen geliyor.
That's one carbonara and a bolognese.
Bir carbonara, bir bolonez.
Got it!
Tamamdır!
Thank you for waiting.
-Beklediğiniz için teşekkürler. -Teşekkürler.
Here's vongole and rigatoni.
Vongole ve rigatoni hazır.
Fettuccine is ready too.
Fettuccine de hazır.
Got it!
Tamam!
Hey, Rosso.
Hey Rosso.
Where'd you snatch this cute girl from?
Bu tatlı kızı nereden çaldın?
Don't say "snatch," or people will get the wrong idea.
Çaldın falan deme, insanlar yanlış anlayacak.
Anna.
Anna.
I'll take you to a much nicer restaurant than this.
Seni buradan daha güzel bir restorana götüreyim.
How's tonight?
Bu akşam nasıl?
Hey!
Hey!
Lay a hand on our star and you won't get off easy.
Restoranımızın yıldızına dokunursan yakanı bırakmam.
Hey, that crybaby Rosso is acting pretty valiant.
Sulu göz Rosso yine atıp tutuyor.
Anna, that guy was crying the other day while watching a movie on TV at my place.
Anna, o adam geçen gün benim evimde televizyonda film seyrederken ağladı.
Shut up.
Kesin sesinizi.
Another order for squid ink risotto.
Bir mürekkep balıklı risotto daha.
Wow, they're showing Summertime.
Şuna bak, Summertime'ı gösteriyorlar.
What?
Ne?
The old cinema is showing Summertime, see?
Eski sinemada Summertime'ı gösteriyorlar.
Isn't it nice?
Çok güzel, değil mi?
Frankfurt has so many movie theaters.
Frankfurt'ta bir sürü sinema var.
It was on TV the other day.
Geçen gün televizyondaydı.
It was a real tearjerker.
İnsanı göz yaşlarına boğuyor.
Have you watched it?
Seyrettin mi?
I haven't.
Hayır.
I see.
Anladım.
The film takes place in the Italian city of Venice.
Film İtalya'nın Venedik şehrinde geçiyor.
Venice is a port city from medieval times
Venedik, Orta Çağ'dan kalma bir liman kenti
and is called the City of Water.
ve bir adı da Su Şehri.
Oh, really?
Gerçekten mi?
The city was originally built on a lagoon.
Şehir aslında bir lagün üzerine kurulmuş.
That is why a canal runs through the city.
Bu yüzden şehrin içinden bir kanal geçiyor.
I'd love to show you Venice sometime, Anna.
Sana bir gün Venedik'i gezdirmeyi çok isterim Anna.
Have you been there before, Mr. Rosso?
Siz gittiniz mi Bay Rosso?
Yeah.
Evet.
The music in that film is great too.
Filmin müzikleri de harika.
I bet you've probably heard the theme song of the movie before too.
Eminim filmin jenerik müziğini daha önce duymuşsundur.
How does it go?
Nasıl?
Let's see…
Bir düşüneyim…
What?
Ne?
I have an idea!
Bir fikrim var. Filmi şimdi izlemeye gitsek ya.
I think we can still get in.
Bence hâlâ girebiliriz.
Yes, but…
Evet ama…
Oh, right.
Doğru.
We'd get out late if we see it now.
Şimdi girersek geç saatte çıkarız.
Yeah.
Evet.
I'm back.
Ben geldim.
Oh, welcome back.
Hoş geldin.
Oh, I'll do that.
Bırakın, ben yaparım.
It's fine.
Gerek yok.
I'm sorry for taking the afternoon off from the restaurant every day.
Geçen gün öğleden sonra izin aldığım için kusura bakmayın.
It's fine.
Sorun değil.
There's not much going on at this hour anyway.
Bu saatte çok fazla kalabalık yok.
I don't mean to pry…
Burnumu sokmak istemem
but where are you going every day?
ama her gün nereye gidiyorsun?
Oh, forget I asked.
Sormadım say.
You're free to use your free time as you wish.
Boş vaktinde istediğini yapabilirsin.
Shooting practice.
Atış talimine gidiyorum.
Shooting?
Atış talimi mi?
Yes, at Mr. Wenkel's shooting range.
Evet, Bay Wenkel'in poligonuna.
Yeah, he's a good guy.
Evet, iyi adamdır.
Have you ever fired a gun before, Mr. Rosso?
Daha önce silah ateşlediniz mi Bay Rosso?
A gun? Absolutely not.
Silah mı? Ateşlemedim tabii.
Just looking at one makes me tremble in fear.
Silah görmek bile beni korkutuyor.
Here you go.
Buyurun.
Enjoy.
Afiyet olsun.
Thanks.
Teşekkürler.
I wonder how it is this time.
Acaba bu kez nasıl oldu.
Give it a taste.
Tadına bak.
What does it taste like?
Nasıl olmuş?
There's garlic, olive oil, parsley, and…
Sarımsak, zeytin yağı, maydanoz ve…
You can't taste the other ingredients, right?
Diğer malzemelerin tadını alamıyorsun, değil mi?
Right.
Hayır.
Then it's not real pasta.
O zaman gerçek bir makarna olmamış demektir.
This is tough.
Zor bir işmiş.
Everything comes with training.
Her şey için eğitim gerekir.
Mr. Rosso, you can take a bath now.
Bay Rosso, banyoya girebilirsiniz. İyi geceler.
I can't believe such a film existed when I was young.
Gençliğimde böyle bir filmin olmasına inanamıyorum.
Mr. Rosso, you always cried as you watched films.
Bay Rosso, film izlerken hep ağlarsınız.
Yeah.
Evet.
I had no time to watch them when I was young, even if I wanted to.
Gençliğimde istesem de izleyecek vaktim yoktu.
I ate so many delicious foods back then,
Eskiden çok leziz yemekler yedim
but I don't remember the taste of a single dish.
ama tek bir yemeğin bile tadını hatırlamıyorum.
I didn't even know the taste of sugar.
Şekerin tadını bile bilmiyordum.
The taste of sugar?
Şekerin tadını mı?
You know about me, right?
Sen beni biliyorsun, değil mi?
After you left, I looked into you as well.
Sen gittikten sonra ben de seni araştırdım.
Nina Fortner.
Nina Fortner.
You went missing after your parents were killed by an unknown individual.
Anne baban bilinmeyen biri tarafından öldürüldükten sonra kayboldun.
What did you want with me?
Benden ne istedin?
Did you have a job for me?
Bana iş mi verecektin?
Did you want me to teach you?
Sana öğretmemi mi istedin?
I thought about having you teach me.
Sizden öğrenmeyi düşündüm.
How did you know about me?
Benim kim olduğumu nasıl öğrendin?
There was a professor researching you at my university's law school.
Üniversitemin hukuk fakültesinde bir profesör sizi araştırıyordu.
The Ristorante Nino incident.
Nino Restoranı olayı.
The Sacco Milano incident.
Sacco Milano olayı. Bay Sabatini'nin bombayla öldürülmesi.
Each case was a murder conducted through different means,
Her olay farklı şekilde işlenmiş cinayetlerdi
and he was called as a witness.
ve o adam tanık olarak çağrıldı ama delil yetersizliği nedeniyle
However, that professor thought of an interesting theory.
Ama profesörümün ilginç bir teorisi var.
Based on that theory,
O teoriye göre…
you were undoubtedly a professional hit man.
…siz profesyonel bir suikastçısınız.
And an elite one at that.
Hatta üst düzey bir suikastçı.
How many people do you think I've killed?
Sence kaç kişiyi öldürmüşümdür?
To be honest, I don't even remember myself.
Açıkçası ben de hatırlamıyorum.
It was when I was still a kid.
Daha küçük bir çocukken başladım.
Before I knew it, I had joined an organization.
Bir bakmışım bir örgüte katılmışım.
Stealing. Blackmail.
Hırsızlık, şantaj.
I'd do anything.
Ne olursa yapıyordum.
And in the end, I became a hit man,
Sonunda suikastçı oldum.
since I'd get to eat good food as a reward.
Ödül olarak güzel yemekler yiyebildim.
It was no big deal.
Büyütülecek bir şey değildi. Çalışıyordum.
It was just like any other day.
Yine sıradan bir gündü.
The same as always.
Her zamanki gibiydi.
It was a café in broad daylight.
Gündüz vakti bir kafeydi.
This stranger from who knows where was my next hit out of countless others,
Nereli olduğunu bilmediğim bir yabancı sayısız hedeflerimden biriydi.
That stranger had ordered a coffee.
O yabancı, kahve söylemişti.
Then, he started putting in sugar.
Sonra şeker atmaya başladı.
One spoonful.
Bir kaşık.
Two spoonfuls.
İki kaşık.
Three spoonfuls.
Üç kaşık.
Four spoonfuls.
Dört kaşık.
When he put in his fifth spoonful of sugar,
Beşinci kaşık şekeri attığında
the taste of the coffee I usually drink spread through my mouth.
hep içtiğim kahvenin tadı ağzıma geldi.
That stranger enjoyed it as he drank.
O yabancı adam
So I lowered my gun.
Ben de silahımı indirdim.
That's all it took.
Sadece bu olay yetti.
That's what made me stop killing.
İnsan öldürmeyi böyle bıraktım.
For those six months,
O altı ay boyunca
why didn't you ask me to teach you how to kill?
sana insan öldürmeyi öğretmemi neden istemedin?
Because…
Çünkü…
I felt that I shouldn't drag you into this.
Çünkü sizi bu işe karıştırmak istemedim.
Do you absolutely have to go?
Gerçekten gitmen gerekiyor mu?
Goodbye.
Hoşça kalın.
Thank you, Mr. Rosso.
Teşekkürler Bay Rosso.
Killing someone is simple.
Birini öldürmek basittir.
All you need to do is forget the taste of sugar.
Tek yapman gereken şekerin tadını unutmak.